Take a nap.

error: ID-10-T

error: user IQ below system minimum spec

Are you drunk?

Now you'll waste another 3 to 5 seconds of your time :)

Hey! It's me, the dwarf who lives in the computer!!
Your answer is, of course, correct! You're a GENIUS.
Listen, I have something to do right now, something important, you know?
I'm gonna shut down the computer. I'll be back tomorrow.
Go do something else! Thanks for understanding, bro.

Going offline to recover from that answer.

The electrons are disappointed in your performance.

You do math like a dairy farmer!